hello YouTube this is my appeal video
and I'll be using English language as
the language in this video this is my
channel URL and this is the reviewer
feedback I got after applying for
monetization I got a feedback that my
content is reused and I think it's a
mistake because I create my videos from
scratch so I'll show you how I create
the videos so yes all of these videos
that here I made all of them so I'll
just show you you how I make these
videos like this video on how to craft
an an impactful elevator
[Music]
pitch so your elevator page or your
mission statement you see we have a
number of live sessions that we had in
the past so I just go there and I listen
to it and I pick the part that I want I
just snipe out the audio that I want
from the particular recording and then I
get to work with it so this is an
example so your elevator page or your
mission statement should be you know it
should be clear it should be short
you're not giving anybody like a so what
I do is to snipe out the part of that
recording that I want to work with and
then I go to cap cut so cap cut is the
major tool with which I make the videos
I go to cap cut so as I working with the
audio that I have sniped from that
recording sometimes it is live sessions
that we had on YouTube some other time
it could be prayer sessions that we have
for like straight one hour sometimes we
I have to use our podcast because we
have podcast recordings on our website
our website is Caris
folks. G Caris folks. org so I head over
to the website and then I listen to the
podcast recordings that we have there
some other time it could be sessions
that we have in our WhatsApp community
and we had a guest speaker so whichever
one it is I get to listen to it and then
I snipe out the part of the audio that I
want to work with and then I go to look
for for videos on pexels I relate with
whatever it is that is been spoken about
in the recording so that everything can
syn I get my free videos from pexels I
work with cap cut to edit the videos so
yes this is cap cut and for that very
video I showed you this is how I work on
it I extract the audio here and then I
put my text I put sound then for these
videos I go to pexels to get these
videos I get my videos from pexels so
like for this video of this um those two
persons I can just come here I type in
my keyword and then I start searching
for the video and yes this is the video
so I get the video I click on it and
then I download the video right so it's
just going to load up now it's a free
download so I get this free videos this
free stock videos from pexels I just
download the video it gets downloaded
into my device then I head over back to
cap cut insert the video there and then
I work on it I do the same thing for all
all other stock videos that I work with
I get all my stock videos from pexels I
work with majorly pexels and capup cut
this is how I get to work on the videos
and then we just have the video all come
out beautiful like this all right so I
do I do the editing the text editing the
sound editing I do everything all on cap
cat I do everything all on cap cut you
see all these videos that are here
everything was made using the exact
procedure that I just shared with you
the same process nothing changed get the
snipet of the audio recording and then
get stock videos from pexels and edit
the videos with cap cut so YouTube this
is how I make the videos for car folks
thank you so much